Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): All right, guys, June is over. It's July 1st. That means step aside, homos. The heteros are back. By the way, did anybody else notice that Pride Month seemed a little bit dialed down this year? Like maybe they weren't feeling
Speaker 2: as proud? Let's talk about that. And speaking of Pride Month no more, let's get the sad news out of the way. Brigitte Macron may lose her coveted status as the first man of France.
Speaker 2: Because elections are underway and Macron has been defeated by Le Pen's party in the first round. And as to be expected, Paris is on fire. But first, I learned something from a flat earther over the weekend who messaged me on Manette, and I cannot wait to share it with
Speaker 3: you guys. All that and more coming up on Candace.
Can you
Speaker 4: guys imagine being married to me? My poor husband, he rolls over. He's like, what are you reading? And I feel like a regular
Speaker 2: wife says something. I don't know, maybe a love series. Nora Roberts sweeping her away.
Speaker 2: Me, on the other hand, he rolled over, he asked me, and I said, I'm reading a flat earth
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): theory. And
it dawned
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): into an entire conversation. He's like, why are you reading a flat earth theory? And I'm like, because
Speaker 2: somebody messaged me on Manect about it, and they included some links, and I'm just reading them. I don't know. I'm just an interested person. No matter what, if there's a bunch of people that believe something, I now want to know what it is that they believe.
Speaker 2: And, of course, he pushed me on this, and he was talking about the earth curvature and science, and I said to him, listen, I'm not a flat earther, I'm not a round earther. Actually, what I am is I am somebody who has left the cult of science. I have left the megachurch of science, because what I have now realized is that science, what it is actually, if you think about it, is a pagan faith.
Speaker 2: I'm going to give you an example of exactly what it is I'm talking about in case you think you disagree.
A woman
Speaker 2: tweeted this. You may have seen me retweet this over the weekend. Her name is Beth. She wrote this. Years ago, I was assured that an IUD was safe, effective, and could be removed at any point if I decided on having more children. It was FDA approved, after all. Ovarian cysts, surgery, infections, a week in the hospital, and infertility.
That
Speaker 2: was what they meant by safe and effective. And this really hit home for me, and I felt tremendously compassionate for her because I'm obviously of the baby-making age, and so many of my friends are similarly going through fertility
Speaker 6: issues and similarly realizing that the birth control that they have been given has contributed to that in some way. People that have pelvic inflammatory disease because of the IUD device being in them for decades. And for those of you who are not aware of what that is, it's literally a copper device that is inserted into a woman to make it so that she...
Speaker 2: not become pregnant. It's birth control. And yes, it is marketed as both safe and effective. All the best stuff, by the way, is marketed as safe and effective. And I was saying to my husband how it's
Speaker 6: become such a difficult topic to talk about because I am compassionate for my friends that are going through
Speaker 2: this. But then there's another side of me that is just amazed, confounded. And
I
How
Speaker 2: could any person get to a point where a
Speaker 6: doctor tells them that putting something that is copper inside of them for a long period of time is perfectly safe and effective and will have no long-term side effects without that person being told the information, just having something that comes online inside, something spiritual, maybe as opposed to referring to it as your gut instinct,
Speaker 2: we should refer to it as the Holy Spirit. It sort of takes you and goes, you know, that actually makes no sense.
Speaker 2: I have suffered from this condition of not trusting
Speaker 6: authorities when they say something to me that is so obviously stupid my entire life.
And I
Speaker 6: contribute that
Speaker 2: maybe to coming from the school of hard knocks. Genuinely, I think that I'm grateful. I am grateful for having gone through the school of hard knocks because you are required to have an element of common sense in order to survive. And when I look at people and they hold on to, but the doctor said this, but the experts said this,
and I said,
Speaker 2: see how extreme the things that they will do they were masking two-year-olds because doctors said no this person if they breathe it's going to be a bad thing well i realized that that's a faith
Speaker 6: that is a faith and it is not a science and regarding a common sense to that exact same effect my husband showed me a clip of andrew tate and he was similarly discussing the covid he was also one of the voices that was telling people hey maybe don't just trust the experts
Speaker 6: on this one before it was cool to say it. I think it was maybe just me and the Tate brothers. He's the second most Googled man in
Speaker 2: the entire world. I know a lot of people feel that they don't understand why he has the platform that he has, but I found this clip to be extremely interesting. Take a listen. One
of my
Speaker 7: habits now is ignoring all data. It's great.
I love when
Speaker 8: people come to me and say, "Actually, we've got the data to prove." To prove what, you little? What are you gonna
prove to me?
Speaker 9: I can prove to you that the ice caps are melting.
There's ice in my
Speaker 10: water right now. I'm gonna leave the water unattended until the ice melts. Will the water overflow out of the cup? No.
Why are
Speaker 11: all the richest, most important people in the world who are pushing this scam buying beachfront homes?
Oh, but the
Speaker 12: data says.
The data's
Speaker 12: from the matrix and you are the matrix and the matrix is full of life.
Anyone who
Speaker 13: actually analyzes the data nowadays proves they're a
Speaker 14: dumbass. Have you seen that graph thing, that meme where you have the most stupid people and the most intelligent people do the same thing. Then you have the midwit in the
middle.
Speaker 14: Data is for midwits, you
Speaker 15: know? Well, the data says,
Speaker 16: you know, the
data says.
Speaker 15: Well, actually, I guess, statistically,
the pharmaceutical
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): company who sells the jab made the data, why are you even reading it? Why are you reading
it? There
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): were stupid people who sat there and said, "The jab's made of 5G cellular data."
And then there
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): was extremely
Speaker 10: intelligent
people like
Speaker 10: me who said,
Speaker 10: "I don't trust these motherf*****ers." And we both didn't get the jab. All the people in the middle were like, "Well, the data says, and the news said." They wouldn't just make us all take a jab for no
reason.
Speaker 13: Jabby jab, jabby jab.
If you even look at data
Speaker 13: nowadays, you're a dumbass.
You
Speaker 10: should just know. Street smart people don't need data. We've just been around, you know? I've just been around. I just know
Speaker 18: things
Speaker 2: because I've just been around.
Speaker 2: honestly that is so relatable to me i can't even explain it i just know things because i've been around because there are so many scenarios i find myself in where i'm unable to articulate the point i'm unable to articulate the natural reaction that i have when somebody tries to sell me garbage i can't articulate it when somebody explains to me
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): well the moon landings definitely happen because this this and the firmament and they could get and i'm just like no i don't know instinctually it just doesn't
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): doesn't register to me it
Speaker 2: just feels like that is a lie and i've realized that i've been thinking deeply about this this pagan cults that we
Speaker 6: exist in it is backed by a false science deity that is what it is it is the science oh this is this is the new god and it is incredible to see the ways in which people worship this deity right climate change
Speaker 6: Unbelievable. People skipping school. People crying, convinced these students that the world's going to be over in 10 years, despite all of the evidence that this lobby has lied to them repeatedly over decades. They still believe it because it's not a science. It's a faith.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Vaccines. I was legitimately raised to believe that my children
Speaker 6: would die unless I offered to the god of science their bodies.
So
Speaker 6: they could just get jabs on jabs. What is it, like 74
Speaker 2: jabs now that children have to get from the time they're born until they graduate high school?
And then I decided
Speaker 2: I wasn't going to do any of that.
And I
Speaker 2: have the healthiest kids in the entire world, three of them. So, yeah, I did not sacrifice my children to that deity. I still get called names for it, and I don't care. Abortion. Yep, I remember that one. I remember when the science god, the science deity,
Speaker 2: told me in school that it was a clump of cells. The science was in. It's a clump of cells. So for the first 12 weeks, it doesn't
Speaker 6: count. And by the way, you should sacrifice your offspring just like the Aztecs did for rain. You should sacrifice your offspring so that it rains money in your life. Think about your future. Think about how much more money you will have if you don't have a child. And people do it for their
Speaker 3: careers. And then
Speaker 3: When my husband and I were in that conversation and he started talking, speaking to me about, you know, the earth
Speaker 2: curvature and all that stuff, what I offered back to him, not because I believe in flat earth, but just because I disbelieve the notion that science
Speaker 6: is ever settled. I said to him, I can imagine 60 years from now where there will be a couple sitting in bed and they will there will be someone explaining to them how the science proves that transgenderism is real.
Because
Speaker 6: it's happening right now. That is another pillar of the pagan faith that has been established. And
Speaker 2: now you have corporations requiring people to say happy pride on the way out in June because they understand that psychology is a part of the game and they will make up the science. They will find the science so that you learn in school how educated you are when you hold these specific positions.
Speaker 2: And
Speaker 6: don't even get me started on history. Don't even get me started on history. Lie upon, lie upon, lie. I
think the
Speaker 6: thing that broke me historically was learning about what they did, what we did, the allies, to the Germans. Unimaginable. Unimaginable that all we're learning about is the Holocaust. And then we allowed what happened to 12 million Germans thereafter who were put into concentration camps, tortured, raped, had their children killed.
And
Speaker 6: we believe that we are the good guys or something like that. And so now I ask this question to myself, literally, why was I put into public school? Why are we all put into public school? And the answer is obvious, to be programmed, to be indoctrinated, to be baptized into this pagan faith. This is why the longer
Speaker 2: people stay in school, it seems the dumber they become.
And
Speaker 2: the more committed they also become to this church of humanism, because that's ultimately what it is. They place their faith in humans,
Speaker 6: while at the same time, bizarrely mocking Christians. It just keeps turning out that if you follow the Bible, if you believe in biblical
Speaker 2: scripture, your life gets better and better and better. But no, they place their faith in something else.
Speaker 2: That they can't quite explain,
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): but they trust implicitly. Their faith is in the CDC, the FDA, the LGBTQIA, the IPCC, the CIA, the FBI. And even in the
face of
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): overwhelming evidence that
Speaker 2: they're being lied to,
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): that their children
and
Speaker 2: their families are becoming sicker, both mentally and physically, the society around them is in full decline. They still keep the faith.
They keep
Speaker 20: the
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): faith.
And they
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): continue to mock the Christians because how backwards, how archaic is the Bible? The Bible is crazy. But check out my textbook on gender
Speaker 21: theory. I'm so smart. Just
food for
Speaker 22: thought, people. Really think about that. Think about whether or not you were pledged into a faith unwittingly, because I think we all were just
Speaker 23: a little bit.
So
Speaker 3: moving on, but also speaking on the topic of faith, it is a good
Speaker 2: time. And I love seeing your comments that people are just starting to go to church because you realize we're fighting real demons, not the fake kind. Well, a good time to get started is now. It's summer. And like
many
Speaker 3: of you, I intend to spend more time with my family, getting outside, traveling, letting go of some of the
Speaker 6: routine. But one routine that I will never let go of is my prayer routine. I'll be continuing my daily habit of prayer with Hallow, the number one prayer app in the world.
Speaker 3: I love Hallow because it's a great resource for the entire family to connect more with God. If you're looking for a place to start, check
Speaker 2: out their new scripture series on the Gospel of John with biblical scholar Jeff Cavins and Jonathan Rumi, who portrays Jesus in The Chosen, or some new
Speaker 6: upcoming content with Jim Caviezel, the actor from Sound of Freedom and The Passion of the Christ.
Speaker 6: Using this app is such a great way to spend a few minutes a day meditating on scripture and talking to God about what he wants for your life. Prepare your mind and heart for the chaos of this world by building your foundation of daily prayer today on Hallow. Download it for free
Speaker 2: for three months at hallow.com slash Candice. That's hallow.com
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): slash Candice. All right, guys, now it's time to get into some stories.
All
Speaker 2: right. Before we get into this first story, you know what I'm going to say. Hit the subscribe button. Also turn on notifications on YouTube because
I did
Speaker 2: do kind of a surprise Sunday sermon I brought to
Speaker 6: you when I learned from my priest that morning. And I want to
do more
Speaker 6: of that, just kind of jumping and doing lives on YouTube. Also, if
we are
Speaker 6: close to million subscribers, that means that we are close to discontinuing the Standis Cup. So head over to clubcandis.com and supports
my
Speaker 6: independence. All
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): right. So I noticed, and I'm sure you noticed as well, the pride felt a little less proud of this month. I don't know.
It just
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): felt like people were maybe feeling the opposite, like ashamed. And as I have always maintained, I have people in my life who are gay, people in my life who are lesbian, and they don't behave like this.
So it
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): became very clear that something else was going on under the guise
of pride. And
Speaker 2: this is how they always get people.
Speaker 6: figure out some attribute about you. What race are you, okay, you're black. Now we're going to make you a crazy person for BLM. So you're gonna burn down things for us on command 'cause you're gonna go racism, racism. And they obviously did this with the gay community and they basically were like, no matter what, you're gonna have to defend whatever happens during the month of June or else.
I
Speaker 6: don't know, those conservatives are going to take everything away from you. And what ended up happening
Speaker 2: was some people with some questionable taste started taking the main stage during Pride. So I'm going to apologize for me showing you an example of that. This is...
I'm a
Speaker 2: proud man performing, I guess, because it's Pride Month. I'm going to first and foremost say viewer discretion, very much advised. And if you are listening
Speaker 6: to this on audio, you have been spared, but not too spared, because I'm going to describe what I am seeing.
Take a
Speaker 6: listen.
Speaker 24 (lower-pitched voice): I'm
a proud man performing, I guess, because it's Pride Month.
Speaker 24 (lower-pitched voice): So what we've
Speaker 2: got going on there is an extremely large person who, of course, is wearing latex and is
Speaker 6: virtually naked because for whatever reason, pride meant being naked. It just became synonymous with being naked. And really what was happening is you had a bunch of men who
Speaker 2: were living out fetishes.
Speaker 2: That is what Pride Month came about. It became Fetish Month, and you would have people feeling like they had to defend these sorts of
Speaker 6: actions. And I think, like I said, what ended up happening is people began pulling back and recognizing that their identity was being used against
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): them to almost act like a cover for people that were actually upped to—
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): evil, right? You should never, ever, ever, whenever
Speaker 2: there's a person telling you to only see yourself within the confines of your identity, whether
Speaker 6: it's your race or sexuality, you should immediately become suspicious, especially if the corporations get involved, especially when the corporations back it
Speaker 2: up, when they're going BLM and they've got the fist bumping or pride and rainbows. You should recognize that there is something more sinister going on. And the thing that is
Speaker 2: sinister that's going on is whatever is antithetical to the Bible is being promoted.
So I
Speaker 2: will say this over and over again, if you are a person and you view yourself to be a non-believer, you should
Speaker 6: realize that this entire Western perception, this new atheistic, the dawn of atheism that we are living within right now, it's very new to the world, as Tucker Carlson said. This is very new
Speaker 2: to the world. It's almost as if
we are
Speaker 2: a unique experiment.
Speaker 2: And if you have a question, you go, well, how do I know God is real? Well, something that should maybe register you as common sense
is that
Speaker 2: the people in charge are specifically doing everything in our society that is antithetical to the Bible. It's like they know God is real. And so the way that they are combating him is introducing the exact opposite of everything that we learn in the Bible, right? So the Bible says marriage is between a man and a woman. Well, what we know that the Satanists that are running our society are going, no, actually, it can be between everyone and anyone. And why not between
Speaker 2: a horse and a human, because that seems to be where we are headed specifically. Don't you think it's also interesting that for pride, they chose the rainbow? Oh, okay. So something that we understand from the Bible to be a promise from God following a flood, they have decided to pervert that. If they weren't so intentional about trying to attack Christianity, you might be able to hold on to the belief that God isn't real.
Speaker 6: But once you start paying attention, you notice the Christian conspiracy, it never leaves you.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): So it seems that some people are definitely dwindling in their support for pride. Maybe we can convert them into
Speaker 25: supporting things like family, like life, like birth, like supporting pre-born. Because according to
Speaker 6: a recent report, Planned Parenthood continues to rake in billions despite dwindling clients. The biggest takeaway is that Planned Parenthood is generating vast profits, including millions in taxpayer funding. But with pre-born, that's you and me, we are actively able to steal their clientele. Meaning...
Speaker 6: that we get to take away those babies that they are trying to kill and offer them life. Preborn operates on a very slim budget. I always tell you guys that. And what they do is just so impactful. They rescue over 200 babies' lives every single day with no government funding, by the way. Preborn's network of clinics are situated in the darkest corners of the nation, and they compete head-to-head with the abortion giants. They need our help now more than ever.
Speaker 6: When you donate just $28 to Preborn, you will offer a free ultrasound to an expectant mother that's caught in a crisis. Because once she hears her baby's heartbeat and she sees that precious life, her baby's chance of life doubles. So sponsor a precious baby's life today. Your tax deductible gift will go directly towards saving baby's lives. Just dial pound 250 and say the keyword baby. That's pound 250 baby. Or
Speaker 2: you can head to preborn.com slash Candace. That's preborn.com
Speaker 2: All right,
Speaker 6: moving on, you guys, because I don't know what's going on in France, but I can tell you that
Speaker 2: Brigitte Macron—I don't know how long Brigitte Macron is going to be leading the country behind her husband, but they had elections last night, or they had the first round of elections, I should say. Their system runs a little bit differently than ours, and it turns out that—
Speaker 2: Marine Le Pen's party looks like they are going to win. I mean, they
Speaker 6: issued a resounding defeat of Macron. So just a little bit of a backstory here. Macron called for a snap election after a poor showing in the EU polls. And the results have indicated that Macron is going to have to share governing responsibilities with Marine Le Pen's far right group. That's what we're terming it, a far right group.
So
Speaker 6: what's really happened, obviously, recognizing that the
Speaker 2: country is taking a turn to the right, is people came out and decided to protest.
And who
Speaker 2: these people are, nobody knows. I personally don't. I don't think these are French people no more than I believe that Antifa burning down everything every time Trump did something was American people. I genuinely believe that when you're seeing these protests and things that are being burned to the ground, it is it should be obvious to you that it's being backed by the government because these things just don't seem to happen. Yeah.
Speaker 2: when the people are upset. So it's amazing the government will show up in force if you step out of line during COVID. Oh, you passed the COVID curfew? Yeah, the French police are going to be out there beating you into submission. But if Paris is burning down right now, suddenly they seem to take a backseat and allow it to happen. So let me show you some
Speaker 26: images coming out of Paris right now. Here's a video.
Speaker 28: and of
Speaker 6: course as always these people are masked i again will always believe that these people are feds and when the government loses power the deep state so to speak loses any power it is a way of them sending out a force of people to make it seem as though it's the actual citizens that are upset about these things when no the citizens voted and
Speaker 6: And this is what they want. They do not like Macron because he was an absolute psychopath during COVID. I actually believe he was raised up to be a psychopath. If you're following the Brigitte Macron story, it's a weird thing to marry the person who raped you statutorily. I believe Macron has no power. I think Brigitte has been running the show. And I also...
am
Speaker 6: a person who believes that Brigitte Macron is a man. I actually know Brigitte Macron is a man. Any rational person who reads the piece that was brought forth by Xavier Poussard comes to the exact same conclusion, which lets you know that there is something very sinister going on in France. And I find these results to be extremely promising. I think the French people have been oppressed for a very long time by their media and by the government and the union between the two constantly lying about the French people. So hopefully the
Speaker 2: Hopefully, this is going to represent some sort of a turning point. All right, guys, I want to get into this clip that I saw on the Internet because I just thought it was really bad advice. Maybe it wasn't even meant to be advice, actually. Let me frame this so it's fair. It's Tia Laurie. You might remember her from Sista. Sista.
I
Speaker 6: loved that show when I was growing up, and I loved the twins, and now they're grown up, and they're
Speaker 2: married, and Tia Laurie was married, and then she got divorced.
Speaker 2: And so now it's become very fashionable, speaking of things that are antithetical to the Bible, for people to speak about their divorces in a way that feels empowering, like they're basically promoting divorce in a weird way. And I don't I don't mean to use her to attack her personally because she is just a symptom of a disease that is happening in our society.
Speaker 2: And I genuinely feel bad for her when I listen to this clip, but I'm going to allow you to listen
Speaker 6: to how she answered the question, how did you know that your marriage was over? And she was asked this by Hoda and
Speaker 29: Jenna of The Today Show. Take a listen.
I knew
Speaker 30: when I really started to focus on my happiness. I feel like women, we tend to
Speaker 31: focus on everybody else's happiness, making sure that everybody else is okay. But at the end of the day, it's about self-love. And when you start to really work on yourself, love yourself, know your value, know your worth, and then all of a sudden there's this awakening. And it's not easy.
Speaker 31: It's a hard journey, but at the end of the day, I feel like it is so, so worth it. Okay,
a
Speaker 3: lot happening there. First and foremost, again, just trying to be kind here. Somebody is asking her a question about her divorce,
Speaker 6: and she is required to answer the question, I guess, in some capacity that feels good to her. What's also disturbing about this clip, though, is that it's being shared by an Instagram account called Divorce Empowered. Like, who is the person who decided to start...
Speaker 6: Instagram account entitled Divorce Empowered. Yeah, you should be empowered about your divorce. And this is why they're sharing the clip, because this is her viewpoint that she started taking care of herself. And she says at the end of the day, it's about self-love, which, by the way, self-love is just a euphemism for selfishness. It's complete and utter selfishness. It's believing in yourself above all else. And oh, my gosh, you know,
Speaker 2: when I was in my marriage,
I
Speaker 2: realized I was taking care of everybody else, and then I needed to start taking care of myself. And the more I started taking care of myself, the more I became selfish, I realized that my marriage was over. Yeah, that actually makes a lot of sense because at the end of the day, that actually isn't what marriage or family is about at all. It's the exact opposite. It's sacrificing, and I say this in the best way
Speaker 6: possible. When you are living that life for you, for you, for you,
Speaker 6: not happiness. It is not. Living for others is actually what happiness is. Living for your faith, that is true happiness. I mean, there is nothing better than the time that I spend invested in my children and invested in my husband. I never think of it as me separate from them.
Speaker 6: because
Speaker 2: you're in a union. You come together. Two become one. And at the moment that you're supposed to be one and you start thinking yourselves as two, you can see why people take that easy option of divorce. It's the worst advice ever. When someone starts telling you to care about yourself and to care about self-love, what they are putting you on a path for is loneliness.
Because
Speaker 2: that's where it ends up. When you are all about yourself, then you need to be alone. This is what happened in her marriage. This is what she's
Speaker 6: sharing. I don't say this, by the way, to discount that obviously it takes two to tango. I am sure that she went through some really hard things in her marriage. I am not painting this as
if her
Speaker 6: husband is perfect. I am definitively sure her husband is not. But this cannot be the message that is out there and the message that
Speaker 2: is
Speaker 2: Young women watching this, seeing this clip, and thinking, I can do bad all by myself. And yeah, actually, you can. You will do badly in life when you are all by yourself. You will not find happiness when you are only living for you.
Speaker 2: That's just not the way to do it.
There are
Speaker 2: tons of wonderful things about being in a union. And one of the things that's good about being in
a union
Speaker 2: is that, you know, it makes it a little easier to live when you're talking about just the expenses. That was like the best thing about coming together with my husband. I was like, yes, I have somebody who can help me with expenses and finances. And I think a lot of people are realizing that more than today that you need a partner, especially in today's economic climate.
Speaker 2: When people are facing the challenges of managing monthly expenses, high credit card interest rates, people feel trapped in a cycle of debt with balances that seem to persist month after month. And there are a lot of people that are listening to this show that are probably only paying the minimum each month, which means that it could take years to become debt free. So do me a favor. Reach out to American Financing. If that's you.
Speaker 2: I want you to reach out to American Financing. They are a trusted partner in helping people achieve financial freedom. If you're a homeowner, they can tap into your home's equity and help you eliminate high-interest credit card debt. On average, their customers save $854 per month, which is equivalent to receiving a $10,000 annual raise. The process is straightforward, and it's quick.
Speaker 2: You could close your loan in as little as 10 days. And if you act today, you may not even have to pay your next mortgage payment.
Speaker 6: It costs nothing to see how much you can save. This opportunity to regain control of your finances is too significant for you to ignore. So please call 800-795-1210. That's 800-795-1210.
Speaker 2: Or you can visit AmericanFinancing.net slash Owens. That's AmericanFinancing.net
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): slash Owens.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): All right, guys, now it's time to read some of your comments.
First couple of comments pertaining to
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): the
Speaker 2: not so great debate, I guess, is what this will be remembered between Trump and Biden, because, well, Biden was just not doing too great. This user writes, my father passed away this past January after suffering from dementia. The open mouth, the staring off, the slow gait, all of that is exactly what my dad did close to the end of his life.
Speaker 2: It is such a sad way to end life. Jill Biden should be ashamed of herself for publicly shaming him this way. Yeah. Don't do not take time. Do not forget to take time to reflect on Jill Biden because she is a monster. She is a rare kind of monster. It is very rare that you see a woman that is that hell bent on power that she will just sort of allow her husband to suffer from dementia and enjoy it because she's just, well, as long as I'm the first lady,
Speaker 2: As long as I'm getting on Air Force One, I don't care. And that is her. She cares about the legacy more than she cares about him. She's truly mentally disturbed. She might be the sickest person in the Biden family. And that's a big statement to make because we've got Hunter
Biden as
Speaker 2: well. But I don't even think Hunter Biden would be able to watch his father suffer every single day and hold his hand and pretend that everything was OK. That takes something else. That's like she's a full sociopath. So you are absolutely right. Right.
Speaker 2: Renee writes, I truly believe that the debate was all part of a bigger plan that nobody seems to have eyes to see. Yes, I believe that. I have shared my thoughts that it seems pretty obvious that they had already kind of pressed the button. And by they, I mean the CIA, the deep state have realized that he he cannot do another four years. He quite literally cannot do another four years. His dementia has progressed so much in just the first four years. They can't hide it.
I
Speaker 2: mean, you can't keep coming up with excuses why he's nowhere and why he's falling and why his mouth is gaping and why he can't put together a sentence. And so they just have to replace him with someone else. And I'm fearful of who that person is.
Speaker 6: Ross writes the morals of an alley cat. That's, by the way, what Biden mumbled to Donald Trump.
was
Speaker 6: that supposed to be an insult? America collectively sighed and
Speaker 2: wished it had been the morals of an alley cat itself as a country. Yeah, that insult, which obviously seemed pre-planned, it was very obvious to me that at least he got the questions in advance. It
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): just, nothing landed because even when he was trying to land stuff, he couldn't speak. We
Speaker 32: were dealing with someone who literally couldn't speak. That is what he sounded
Speaker 26: like.
so
Speaker 26: it it just did not land whatsoever we had a couple of comments i'm going to read
Speaker 2: just one of them pertaining to thomas massey's wife i dedicated my mask thomas massey on sunday and i just hope everybody is keeping him and his family in their thoughts and in their prayers sincerely in their prayers not just the meaningless online i'll keep you in my prayers but actually taking time to pray for them because he lost his wife and there have been no details but just knowing that it was his high school sweetheart completely completely tore at me and
This
Speaker 2: person felt the same. She writes, my heart goes out of Thomas Massey's family. I'm also from Kentucky and we lost my mother, also named Rhonda, on June 7th after a 17-year battle with breast cancer. She was a devoted mother and the strongest woman I've ever met. She held on to her beliefs no matter what, and I fully believe she would have loved you had she ever listened. Thank you so much. And again, I hope everybody is just keeping the Massey family
safe.
Speaker 2: in their thoughts and giving meaningful prayers in their direction, sending meaningful prayers in their direction. We have this person who is writing regarding Hallo, speaking of prayers. Hi, Candice. I want to thank you for sharing Hallo with your listeners. I was raised Catholic, going to Sunday school for 13 years, but felt lost in my adult years, 35 years young, on how to become closer with the Lord and how to read the Bible. I'm
going to say,
I downloaded the
Speaker 2: Hallow app a week ago, experiencing an inexplicable sense of urgency within me after hearing you speak of it. I started the Bible in a Year series that day, and wow, has it really woken up to my spirituality again and lit a fire in me for God's word. I have been in prayer almost every morning and night and catch myself thinking about God's word as I go through my day now. Thank you for doing what you do and speaking about Christianity. Christ is king. Love you, Candice. These are the best comments that I receive. I get so many people tagging me saying that they felt compelled to go to church after listening to this show.
Speaker 2: And it makes me feel really good. I have to say that. And I know that it's not something that I'm doing. I feel God at work inside of everyone. It truly is the Holy Spirit. I mean, you look at Russell Brand, so many people that are talking about faith for the first time. And I think it's because everyone is realizing that the satanic church
Speaker 3: of science
works.
Speaker 3: Everything that it has spelled in our society has been demonic like we are we are fighting real demons. I quite literally cannot say that enough.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Lastly, sharing with you one of the many, many flat Earthman X that I received since
I
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): did the live the other day. And again, I I'm not subscribing to the flat Earth theory at all. I just was decided to read an article on it because why not?
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): This person
Speaker 2: writes,
Speaker 2: Once you look, you will see that all of the evidence points to the Earth being flat. The biggest indicators, in my mind, being the fact that we can see objects at a distance that should be hidden behind hundreds of feet by the curve of the Earth, the fact that all modern technology assumes the Earth is a flat topographical plane to function, airplanes, GPS, and the truly hilarious footage and abject lack of proof that we actually went to the moon. Reach out to YouTubers that have done the research for more information. Yeah.
Speaker 2: And he offers some YouTubers. Thanks. Here's what I will say to you. I definitely believe the moon landing was faked. I had no coming back to me after coming back for me after reading chaos and reading something else called a funny thing happened on the way to the moon. It
just I
Speaker 2: don't know. It's always seemed cartoonish to me. But then when you realize the government was up to in the 60s and how they were focused
Speaker 6: on creating a mass psychosis.
Speaker 6: By large events, like seeing how people would react to a
Speaker 2: trauma like the Manson murders or even something which you wouldn't, I guess you wouldn't say is a trauma, but it leaves a huge impression upon you. Like, you know, going to the moon, everybody crowded around watching on a television, like I say.
Speaker 2: chaos is required reading
Speaker 3: for every single person that listens to this podcast you absolutely must read that book because you have to comprehend how sinister how evil and how satanic a government
Speaker 2: is you have to you have to accept that reality and don't worry it doesn't make you sad doesn't make you pessimistic because i'm optimistic i'm a christian i know christ is king i know that in In the end, we win.
Speaker 2: The end. I will see you guys
Speaker 33: tomorrow.